cardstockforteachers.com 2017-11-25

# Cardstock

#### PRIVACY POLICY

Cardstock, LLC (referred to as “Company,” “we,” “us” or “our”) respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your privacy online.  The purpose of this document (the “Privacy Policy”) is to explain to you how we use information that we have collected from and about you. If, after reviewing the Privacy Policy, you have questions about the types of information we collect, how we use it, or similar issues, please contact us at https://www.cardstockforteachers.com/request_info.

This Privacy Policy applies to the services (“the Services”) provided through our website located at https://www.cardstockforteachers.com/ (the “Website”) and all mobile platforms made available by us to deliver the Services. It does not apply to the practices of other companies that we do not own or control nor does it apply to information of any kind provided to us by advertisers or other business partners. Links to other websites are governed by their own policies.

If this Privacy Policy is not acceptable to you, you should discontinue using the Services.

##### The Privacy Policy will let you know:

  * What information we collect from or about you
  * What we use your information for
  * In what ways we may disclose your information to other parties
  * The kinds of security measures in place to protect against loss or misuse of your personal information
  * What cookies are, and other forms of tracking that may be in use on the Website
  * Other privacy policies to which you may become subject when you use the Services
  * How you can access, update or delete your Personally Identifiable Information
  * What happens if we make changes to the Privacy Policy

##### What information do we collect from or about you?

We refer in this Policy to two types of user information: Personally Identifiable Information (sometimes referred to as “PII”) and non-Personally Identifiable Information.

Personally Identifiable Information refers to any information that can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate you. Examples of Personally Identifiable Information include a name, physical address, e-mail address, telephone number, date of birth, or a credit card number.

We collect only the PII that you voluntarily provide to us, such as when you register to use the Services, set up a profile, create content, sign up for a special offer, or complete a survey. If you purchase products or subscribe for paid services, you might also be asked to provide your credit card and related information for billing purposes.

You might also be asked for, or choose to provide, additional information about yourself that does not, itself, specifically identify you. This is non-Personally Identifiable Information. However, some information of this kind, such as your age, gender, geographic location and shopping preferences may be required (or merely requested) when you register for the Services, and may be associated with your PII.

We may also automatically collect other types of non-Personally Identifiable Information as you use the Services, including technical information (such as your IP address, mobile device ID, or browser type) and usage information (such as location data, preferred language, the parts of the Services you have visited, which links you have clicked and other information about how you interact with the Services). This information is anonymous, and is not associated with your PII, although it may be associated with other pieces of anonymous information about you.

##### What do we use your information for?

Your Personally Identifiable Information may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To contact you regarding your account. These communications may include notices regarding changes to our policies, service updates, account management procedures and customer service transactional messages.
  * To e-mail you newsletters or tips about how to use the Services, inform you of product updates, or notify you about our own special offers.
  * To bill your credit card or other specified form of payment, in accordance with the Terms of Service.

Non-Personally Identifiable Information may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To enable us to generate aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction.
  * To customize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
  * To make improvements to the Website and Services
  * To inform potential partners about the size and characteristics of our audience

##### Do we disclose any information to other parties?

We do not sell or trade your Personally Identifiable Information to outside parties. We may disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to vendors who help us operate the Website, conduct our business or provide the Services to you, such as credit card processors, customer service centers, or e-mail marketing providers. All such partners are bound to keep your information confidential.

We may disclose Personally Identifiable Information, including to local, state, or federal law enforcement officials, when we believe in good faith that the law requires such action, or when required to do so by order of a court or other compulsory legal process. We may also share Personally Identifiable Information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, or to prevent harm to the Website.

We may transfer your Personally Identifiable Information if we are acquired by or merge with another company. We will notify you in accordance with the procedures contained in this Privacy Policy if your information will become subject to a different privacy policy.

We may use or distribute information about you and your use of the Services in ways that do not reveal Personally Identifiable Information. For example, we may provide anonymous usage data or summary characteristics of our audience to potential partners, utilize same for internal business or research purposes, or post such information on publicly accessible areas of the Website.

##### How secure is your personal information?

The security of our user data is very important to us. We store your information securely, using industry-compliant encryption technology. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our web forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

##### Do we use cookies or other forms of tracking?

Cookies are small files that a website or one of its service providers transfers to your computer’s storage device via your Web browser (if your browser is configured to permit this) that enable its systems to recognize your browser and store certain information. We use “cookies” to collect information and improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your local device. We may use “persistent cookies” to save your user ID and password for future logins to the Service. We may use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Service.

Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to your computer, and can only be read by a web server of the website that issued the cookie to you.

Depending on your web browser, you may have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers default to accept cookies but enable you to configure settings to decline them. For further information about disabling cookies you can visit www.allaboutcookies.org. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other features of the Services that depend on cookies.

We integrate with tools made available by social media companies such as Facebook and Twitter, in order to offer social features such as content sharing. These companies may use cookies or other tracking technologies in order to recognize you when you use their tools in the future.

We maintain internal logs of usage of the Services. Logs include information such as IP (Internet Protocol) address, browser type and version, and computer operating system. We use logs mainly for internal systems administration and diagnostic purposes, and to detect improper use of the site. Logs may also be used to generate aggregate, non-Personally Identifiable Information for internal use.

We do not use cookies, similar technologies, or its internal logs to associate your Personally Identifiable Information with data about your use of the site.

##### Other privacy policies to which you may be subject

Your use of Twitter and other third-party websites and services which may be linked to the website, and their use and display of the content that you share there is subject to their privacy policies and online terms of use, and is not under our control.

Under the Family Education Rights and Privacy Act (“FERPA”), schools that receive certain federal funds must obtain prior written consent from a parent or guardian of a minor student before disclosing any educational records regarding such student to third parties. However, FERPA allows schools to disclose those records, without consent, to school officials with legitimate educational interests. If FERPA applies to you, you hereby designate Company, its employees, contractors, and agents, as “school officials” who have a “legitimate interest” in using and accessing any education records, and you hereby represent and warrant that (a) you have obtained all consents necessary in connection with disclosing any educational records directly or indirectly to Company, Users, or otherwise in connection with the Services, and (b) the disclosures described in (a) are not and will not be a violation of FERPA.

We hereby represent and warrants to you that (a) we will perform the Services in a professional and workmanlike manner and (b) we will only use and access the Educational Records in accordance with the terms of this Agreement.

EXCEPT AS EXPRESSLY SET FORTH IN SECTION, THE SERVICES, PROFESSIONAL SERVICES, REPORTS, AND ANYTHING PROVIDED IN CONNECTION WITH THIS AGREEMENT ARE PROVIDED "AS-IS," WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND. COMPANY HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, RELATING TO THE SUBJECT MATTER HEREUNDER, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ALL IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE, AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.

Student & Parent Personal Information: We store Student and Parent information, including names, email addresses and ID numbers. Instructors and School staff may in the future enable their own student data to be sent to third-party software, like a gradebook or courseware application. Aside from that, we do not share any personal information with third parties. We are compliant with the U.S. Family Educational Rights & Privacy Act (FERPA). Under FERPA, Schools may disclose, without consent, “directory” information such as a student’s name, address, telephone number, date and place of birth, honors and awards, and dates of attendance. This information is available only to the Instructor and other staff at the same school district if an entire school is enrolled in the system, and depending on the permission settings set by the School or Instructor. Personal information may be seen by our support staff when you ask for technical support. The Website uses password protection, security codes, and encryption to prevent anyone else from accessing personal information.

**USE BY CHILDREN**

The Children’s Online Privacy and Protection Act (“COPPA”) requires that online service providers obtain parental consent or provide notice before they knowingly collect personally identifiable information online from children who are under 13. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from a child under 13, except in the following circumstances:

  * We may collect personal information through the Services from or about a child under 13, including a child’s name (first name and last initial), date of birth, email address or telephone number, and the child’s parent’s email address, where that student’s school, district, and/or teacher has agreed (via the terms described below) to obtain parental consent for that child to use the Services and disclose personal information to us, for the use and benefit of the learning environment.
    * If you are a school, district, or teacher, you represent and warrant that you are solely responsible for complying with COPPA. For more information on COPPA, please [click here](http://www.business.ftc.gov/documents/0493-Complying-with-COPPA-Frequently-Asked-Questions). If you are a teacher, you represent and warrant that you have permission and authorization from your school and/or district to use the Services, and for purposes of COPPA compliance, you represent and warrant that you are entering into these Terms on behalf of your school and/or district.
    * As a school, district, or teacher providing consent on behalf of parents or guardians, in order to create an  account (as described below) you may be required to provide valid school credentials and a valid school email address to verify your identity in order to access and use certain features of the Services.

If we learn we have collected personal information from a student under 13 other than pursuant to the above, or if we learn a student under 13 has provided us personal information beyond what we request from him or her, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that a student under 13 may have provided us personal information in violation of this paragraph, please contact us at https://www.cardstockforteachers.com/request_info or by calling Customer Service at (281) 682-4786.

**How can you access, update or delete your Personally Identifiable Information?**

All account settings can be changed from https://www.cardstockforteachers.com/request_info. This includes reviewing and changing Personally Identifiable Information, setting e-mail preferences for non-account related e-mails, cancelling or deactivating your account.

Administrative and account-related communications are necessary to ensure we provide our users with the highest level of service, therefore registered users are not permitted to opt out from receipt of these communications, except in that event that you cancel your registration for the Services entirely.

New types of marketing communications might be added from time to time. Users who visit the https://www.cardstockforteachers.com/request_info section can opt out of receiving future marketing communications or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive.

Anonymous information relating to your past usage of the Services may remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted, and any content that you have contributed to the Services will remain visible to the same extent as if you remained a registered user of the Website. If you wish to have all information that you have posted to be deleted, please contact us https://www.cardstockforteachers.com/request_info and we will make reasonable efforts to honor your request.

**What if we make changes to our Privacy Policy?**

Because enhancements to the Services we provide may affect the information that we collect and the manner in which we use it, this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. All changes will be incorporated into the written policy and posted here. The date of last revision to the Privacy Policy is indicated at the bottom of this page.

We will provide you with the opportunity to accept or reject significant changes to the Privacy Policy during your next sign-on to the Services. If you do not agree to the modifications, your access to the Services may be discontinued.

**What if you have questions that are not answered here?**

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us using the information below:

Last updated: September 11, 2015
